BABY I’mma MONSTER
I’ve never felt like this before
They stop when I walk through the door
Something click it’s a state of mind
Type of rich can’t be quantified
And it ain’t my fault
if you not trying to match my mood
Sorry but that’s on you
Baby I don’t mean to brag
You know I’m not talking cash
Got a thing that’s only mine
And I watch your eyes go green
I can feel your jealousy
Up here in the sky sky
Oh look at me, I woke up
Feeling like a BILLIONAIRE, woah
World is mine, yeah life is so unfair
Money don’t compare
I got something rare
Feeling like a BILLIONAIRE
I got rules here to break
Say it with my chest and in your face
Hear the boom in the bass
Pump it up, back it up, turn in up
R.U.K.A
ACE-SA be the name, so cut the deck
Deal it out
Above the money power and respect
Arigato
Who dat? who dat? who dat?
Got the flame
Bet it on me, double up your life
Baby I don’t mean to brag
You know I’m not talking cash
Got a thing that’s only mine
And I watch your eyes go green
I can feel your jealousy
Up here in the sky sky
Oh look at me, I woke up
Feeling like a BILLIONAIRE, woah
World is mine, yeah life is so unfair
Money don’t compare
I got something rare
Feeling like a BILLIONAIRE
BILLIONAIRE
Buh buh buh buh BILLIONAIRE
BABYMONSTER
got me feeling like a BILLIONAIRE
BILLIONAIRE
Buh buh buh buh BILLIONAIRE
BABYMONSTER
got me feeling like a BILLIONAIRE
Oh look at me, I woke up
Feeling like a BILLIONAIRE, woah
World is mine, yeah life is so unfair
Money don’t compare
I got something rare
Feeling like a BILLIONAIRE